Hello hello everyone welcome to my channel
Suryavanshi Raj my name is Abhishek Singh and
SP Mode ko * support waiting period in
health insurance, health
insurance has to be done
after taking the policy 100MB topic this mediclaim
insurance policy is started,
insurance is done from someone, from some company, someone
told me that we did it from the bank, then we got the
medical done at the time of taking the policy, there is never any medical condition for
which you have to
wait, okay so that is the
proper guideline of Meghnad You Torch Regulatory and Development Authority of India and it is a
universal truth, everyone does this
for the insurance policy except some points, if
someone is in a private job or there is a
government job, then they have a
corporate plant, it is different, in that you
get the benefit from lemon, okay
but what is here is that your policy to
start, it does not start covering
all the medical conditions immediately till the store with some condition score waiting period,
okay so understand this thing carefully, in
which way you will get medical
insurance and in what way  When and which
disease will it start covering? So first of all, the
health insurance that starts covering you
starts from the dentist. Excellent results,
for example, on
December 31, 2013, I subscribed to my policy. The
policy will start
from January
and from that day onwards, the news will
start coming. Accidental juice for a teaspoon,
only accidental and viral in it, whatever is
my father's addition, will be taken care of.
This accident of a train driver will
not be covered in that seniors insurance
policy. The company will immediately give you the
result for the policy. Please pay 100% attention to
this thing. In case of drink and drive,
you should
not have any chronic dental case from the consumption of benefits, in which accident
needs to be taken care of. Second, 3D
glasses like cancer, it is
okay, cancer, heart attack,
festival,
subscribe [music]
and if
someone already has it and after a month, the
municipality does not support, then this is
in testing condition, I will talk about it further,
please talk about West Indies,
but need not be difficult, one  After the month the
company will start covering it, apart from this,
after 30 days only, whatever
diseases you have, 24 diseases you will have, that
too the company covers after becoming eligible, for example,
dengue, malaria, chikungunya, swine
flu, type 2, jaundice, Covid, all these
things will start getting covered by the husband,
okay,
subscribe to all these,
subscribe, apart from this, there are some people, they
subscribe, they go away after two
to three months, after four months, then after
seeing there they come back, so
what are the problems of those people, I will
also share the equal list with you in my debit card video,
you keep checking and
see together as it
starts from here, first of all if I talk about
piles special, its
waiting period is two years, okay, today
I definitely tried it every day, okay, wash it, I like
31st December 2016, it will start
from 1st January, it will start on Thursday in 2019, 2020,
2026,
okay,
subscribe  Or crack
by Tom Donilon and
[music]
what you'll be seeing on the screen
is sinus, soon
Adnan Sami, ulcers, there are many incarnations,
stomach ulcers, there are many things, all these
things slowing down,
you're fine in this, so pay attention to this thing,
if you go, you take Chauhan Bangar every day
and after six months you'll go for the
opportunity, even on drinking water, there will be
lipstick there and after that you'll think,
hey man, I had a visit while I was on some work,
I don't know why I smoked this cigarette, so
we would immediately tell the company that we'll file a
claim, man, the company is
useless, no, nothing like that happens, I keep
watching this waiting period carefully,
many advisors tell you,
they think that the customer has gone to take the waiting period of the stock market,
even in this case they do
n't tell you the waiting period, but I am
telling you the waiting period for deposit, this is
common in all, it's not that there is some
problem in all and if this starts happening with Dimple, then
you should take it from 4  5 to 10
years old mistakes, you are paying regular
premium for it, what is the need to pay that,
what is the need to pay that, you can save money, if you
take it when a problem arises then you get that
benefit, if I talk about insurance, health
insurance or any other insurance,
we get it when we need it, we get it when
we don't need it,
because insurance means
covering all the uncertainties of life, covering
things that are 100%, so I had an
accident, there is a treatment
button for you Singh Saurabh, no one will cover it
because I can send my pic WhatsApp something in
[music]
so keep this in mind, it is for everyone,
okay, because many people
follow advisories, do many things,
they do not understand the thing and until there is a
problem with the other person, they never
understand that thing, so why today, for some
people,
because whatever you have and
everything with you can end in a minute,
if there can be a medical condition, then keeping this in mind,
definitely keep it with you completely  To do this, you are
good, okay, what is a pre-existing disease?
Prince Skin Disease means
when you take a health insurance policy
and you disclose that you have diabetes,
blood pressure, asthma, BP,
so all these things, all these
medical conditions, while taking a mediclaim policy,
this is the
subscribe in the ghee,
okay, so you see, it does
not contain [music] aloe vera, we take normal,
okay, and
subscribe,
okay, now you are thinking of
subscribing to the company, that
if you have statutory and kidney issues before two-four
years, then we will not cover it, okay, so
there, first of all, the company will
do the watching, due to diabetes,
that element is cut, after this the company will cover,
rest all the best friend, you will get it as it is,
half of the
subscribers, so this is the
disgusting,
okay, the youth
waiting period is meeting, so there is a
difference in the features,
in some you will get post graduation, in some you will
not get it, so this is the difference  Between approximately
I have told that I am Deobandi
after accidental one month practical
signal two years' jhala bank thing rest there is a
little difference in the meeting by extended
complete company which
alarm will have to be set while talking there
you can ask questions
understand the rest is permission but if any
normal if you are going this minute ringtone
price case told you if someone attempts
suicide from there and it happens
okay fuel diagnostic test if
someone is getting front general but if
job body injury es under influence of
alcohol codeine case tell me cosmetic
treatment is called express
Jalandhar North is ready now I am going to get it done
soon after surgery that is not mine
when will it happen then he needs cosmetic surgery okay then
all that is needed otherwise treatment for
weight loss if someone wants to lose weight if there is any
problem then relax drive
with letter example 105 someone has a man
okay then first one has to get the better half done by surgery
all those things are not of the news
this  10,000 The Chanak Explosion in All Health
Insurance Policy Okay, rest whenever you
do MS Word, if you keep it far away from you, the
basic waiting period of 20000,
you have to do this much, which I
told you, thank you so much, a great one, but
thank you so much for watching Suryavanshi
Rajput, thank you so much